Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Okay. we have 21 hostages.
One child. Lina. daughter of Alex Maynard.
Soldier and head of this lab.
Her mother is in the Army.
She brought her to see her dad
when the situation began.
Lone terrorist.
Former lab staff. idealistic type.
He wants all of France to see
the weapons they're designing here.
He's unstable and paranoid.
What goes on in that lab?
We don't know. It's classified.
All I know is that it's explosives.
Same partners as usual.
Usual rules of engagement.
Self-defense. hostage in danger.
or direct order.
The area is potentially explosive.
Hold your fire.
We'll use the service corridors. Let's go!
I want to speak
to the Minister of Defense.
And I want a journalist.
Otherwise. I swear I'll kill someone.
David. Laurent. in position.
Bravo Charlie.
What do I have to do?
Shoot someone?
Is that it?
You have 15 minutes.
Then I kill everyone. Do you hear me?
And don't try to buy time.
I know your tricks.
Okay. I have a visual on the hostages.
No visible injuries.
Do you understand?
Fuck!
Negotiations suspended.
Fuck it!
Visual on the target.
He has a detonator in his left hand.
He looks agitated.
12-gauge pump-action shotgun.
I've had enough.
Don't look at me!
I've lost Oscar 13.
I don't see the girl. I can't find her.
Target is on the move.
Shit!
He's leaving the cafeteria.
Watch out.
Oscar 9 is moving towards the back.
I can't see her.
She's taking a bag.
What the fuck is she doing?
You.
Get up.
Now!
Goddammit!
She has a Beretta.
This is bad. Let's move fast.
Door may be rigged.
We'll go in through the back.
You too! Get up!
Get the fuck up. now!
Fuck!
Police!
-Police!
-It'll be okay. Listen to me.
Target neutralized. One hostage hit.
There! Secure the rear.
-Look at me. honey.
-Sir. we need to evacuate.
We need to apply pressure.
She's been shot.
Follow me. Evacuate!
We've got this. Come on.
Come. We'll handle it.
-Get back. sir!
-She's been shot!
There's a three-minute timer. Evacuate.
Get back. sir!
Ma'am. can you hear me? Can you hear me?
-Keep going.
-Extraction!
Can you hear me?
Don't worry. we'll take care of you.
My daughter…
-Keep moving. Hurry.
-Did you hear me?
I'm sure he set explosives.
Where's your daughter?
Go upstairs. sir. Please.
Laboratory.
In the lab?
-He set explosives.
-We're on it.
-My daughter is in the lab!
-Get him out!
We're on it. Medic!
-Doc! Over here!
-I'm a dad too. ma'am. I'm a dad too.
-I'll go get your daughter.
-My daughter…
Come on. we're evacuating.
Go! Everybody. evacuate!
No. wait! We need to find the girl!
She's missing. Christophe!
You have 90 seconds.
then you need to get out.
We didn't have much time.
so Laurent and I
volunteered to go find the girl.
We headed into the corridors and…
Lina Mayard died
in the explosion that day.
Like Lieutenant Villiers.
Yeah.
Fifteen years ago. tonight.
Is there anything you remember.
any detail you'd like to share with us?
No.
Chloé. let's move on to his wife.
This is Amal Mayard.
She left the army and the country
after her daughter's death.
She was declared dead.
She committed suicide in Türkiye
one year later.
Mayard. however. switched sides.
He served ten years in Bois-d'Arcy prison
for arms trafficking.
Including explosives back then.
That's where he met Kröller.
He got out last November.
No trace of him since.
No digital trail. either.
He used Kröller's network
to assemble the team that stole the CL20.
We believe he's the one who killed Kröller
when we arrested him yesterday.
He still has the 500 kilos.
and he put some of it
in Christophe's ICU room.
I put half of the Intel team on it.
ELITE FORCE
Not bad. right?
Start your engine. Daktari. Let's listen.
-Careful. guys.
-Listen up.
Rev it up a bit.
-Wait.
-Louder.
-Louder?
-Yes.
More?
That noise is killing me. Stop!
Speak up!
-More?
-More!
It's his foot!
Why don't you take your foot off?
Laurent. I can make noise too.
Okay. okay! Hands up!
NATIONAL GENDARMERIE
GIGN
COMMIT FOR LIFE
So. how's the investigation going?
They're making progress. but…
All I wanted was
to be with him at the end.
You got to be with him every day.
They took him from me.
They can't get away with this.
They won't get away with it.
I'll make sure of that.
I've never seen that photo.
We had a barbecue at Christophe's.
You were there. actually.
Yeah. I remember. I was ten. I think.
Yeah.
Do you know why you remember?
No.
Because you drank
an entire glass of wine that day.
Yeah. I remember now.
-My first alcoholic drink.
-Your mom caught us.
My God. she really went off on us.
Sorry.
I'm sorry about Christophe.
As a kid. Dad would take me
to the Chinese buffet in Versailles.
Just the two of us. It was our thing.
Mom didn't like those kinds of places.
I go every year.
on the anniversary of his death.
Usually on my own. but…
Since it's tonight. I thought maybe…
Would you like to come with me?
No.
I never do anything. Ever.
I need to go check something.
Okay.
IGGN breathing down our necks
won't speed things up.
I might have a lead on Mayard.
Are you coming?
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
REPORT NUMBER 1
Okay.
FEBRUARY 10. 2011:
TRESPASSING AT A SECRET DEFENSE FACILITY
VERSAILLES COURT
TWO YEARS IN PRISON
David. I told you.
I'll call you as soon as I have something.
Just checking. You never know.
Well. I've got nothing. You can go now.
Can I take a look?
Sure.
PROPERTIES
LAST ACCESS:
TODAY. FEBRUARY 10. 2025. 2 MINUTES AGO
FEBRUARY 10. 2011:
TRESPASSING AT A SECRET DEFENSE FACILITY
Where are you going?
To the shooting range. You?
Why are your guns in a bag?
You're such a pain.
What did you take? Can I see?
Should I come with you?
You're better off staying put.
With that kind of gear.
it rarely ends well.
Sometimes it's not meant to end well.
SITUATION ANALYSIS
TARGET: VICTOR DUTEL - RETALIATION
ONGOING OR PLANNED OPERATIONS
LT. DAVID BERGER. LT. LAURENT VILLIERS
I followed because you said no.
I figured out where you were going.
We're 10 km from where Dad died.
on the day he died.
Are you going
to pay your respects or something?
Go home. Max.
You know what?
I'm going to pay my respects. too.
Don't worry. not with you.
We'll go in separately. It's fine.
You're right. I am going there.
But it's not about Laurent.
It's about Mayard.
the guy who killed Christophe.
He lost his daughter in the explosion
that same day.
He blames us for her death.
I think he's doing all of this
to avenge her.
Ten years ago. he was arrested
for trespassing on a military base.
It was the same place.
On the same date.
Do you think he'll be there tonight?
I don't know.
You're arresting him alone?
So you didn't get official orders. then?
What are you doing?
This is under the radar. I take it?
No. it's not a mission.
It's not under the radar.
It's nothing. Go home. Max.
In that case. you're not in charge.
That girl died at the same time as Dad.
And you. my Dad's partner. my mentor.
were there. yet you want me out of this?
Here.
What's this?
It's unlisted.
Don't worry.
We're only here to arrest Mayard. right?
Obviously.
It's a ten-minute walk.
Remember how Dad liked riddles?
Yeah.
How do you flush out a terrorist
holed up with no hostages?
Well. how do you do it?
You wait for him to leave.
You and your partner are unarmed.
A terrorist aims at you. What do you do?
-Max.
-Do you know?
Of course I do.
You sacrifice yourself.
You die for them.
You don't die for them.
You trust your partner.
You put your life in their hands.
as they put theirs in yours.
You count on them reacting when you act.
The terrorist can't cover
two fronts at once.
So you need total trust.
Yeah.
You must be sure that no matter what.
you're there for each other.
Was it like that with you and Dad?
That was a long time ago.
On your back. Look out. Come on.
Faster.
Come on. keep your hips up.
Fill your lungs.
Major.
-Go on.
-Major.
I'm kind of busy here.
Where's Commander Berger?
I need to talk to him.
I don't know. He's probably training.
Where is he training?
That's it. PJ. Good job.
Major. it's important. It's about Mayard.
Victor. can you take over?
I don't know. Diving. jumping.
shooting. boxing. tech drills.
We train 24/7. He could be anywhere.
I'm not his mom.
I thought a section leader
trained with his men.
Yeah. but today it's the anniversary
of his partner's death. so…
He does what he has to do.
and I leave him alone. okay?
Excuse me. I have a section to run.
Come on. PJ. keep it up.
Do one more lap.
That's it. fill your lungs…
Is this the lab entrance?
Yeah.
Go.
This is David. leave a message.
DIED IN THE LINE OF DUTY
02.10.2010
February 10.
Shit. February 10.
TRESPASSING
02.10.2011
Get your team ready.
I think I found Mayard.
I think Commander Berger is on his trail.
This is where it happened?
Yeah.
What really happened here?
What do you mean?
Max. your father. Laurent. died.
and we all have to live with it.
-That's what happened.
-That's bullshit.
I read the after-action report.
You were the only one with him.
Why's your report the only one missing?
Why didn't Christophe say anything?
If there's nothing to hide.
where's the report?
I was at rock bottom.
Can you understand that?
Laurent was my best friend.
He was a brother to me.
Police academy. pre-selection. training.
We did it all together.
I was his best man.
I even became his son's mentor.
I didn't write a report
because I wasn't able to.
Satisfied?
I was in the parking lot
on graduation night.
Christophe asked you
if I knew the truth about Dad.
What truth is that. David?
Clear.
Police! Stop!
I'll go left.
Max!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. he went that way.
Max!
Open your mouth.
In the vest?
Yeah.
Shit.
I struggle to remember her face.
You know. my daughter.
This is the only place
I can still picture her.
I get to see her again. but only just.
How are things with your partner?
We tried to save her.
No. you stopped me from saving her.
I could have done it.
Can you imagine losing a child?
-I could've taken more from you.
-You okay?
Yeah.
Your father was a hero.
He really tried to save my daughter
-He gave his life for her.
-Shut up.
On your knees.
Legs crossed behind you.
Hands on your head.
Max.
Will you watch him?
That guy right there
is a coward.
Ever wonder why he made it out
and not your father?
Ever heard of blast-proof armored doors?
Shut it.
No. apparently. you don't know.
They were activated before the explosion.
From the inside.
Only one person made it out. Him.
Unfortunately.
there's only one explanation.
He fled. sealing the blast doors
to save his own ass.
He locked in my daughter and your father.
leaving them to die to save himself.
Max!
Look at me. Max. Listen to me.
I'm the one who shot him.
Okay?
Is that clear? I shot him.
And I was alone.
Okay?
Is it true?
Is it your fault he died?
You don't know what's at stake.
They're on their way.
This is unauthorized. If they find out
you were here and you shot him.
your GIGN career is over.
I don't give a shit about my career!
I want to know what the fuck you did!
Stop acting like a child!
Stop it right now!
This is not the time to argue!
You'll do exactly what I say.
Keep your phone turned off.
Go back to your car.
And go home!
Don't say a word to anyone.
Is that clear?
And you do that right now.
Get out of here!
Subtitle translation by: Alison Simpson
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app